♪〜
〜♪
C'mon, Mom... buy me a gun!
（トニス）
母ちゃん 鉄砲買ってよ
What do you call
that thing in your hand?
（トニスの母）
その手に持ってるのは何？
I mean a different one!
（トニス）こんなのじゃなくて
（トニスの母）
ダメです 我慢なさい
Forget it!
Use the one you have.
Come on, Mom... I'll clean
the thomas coop every day!
買ってよ
トマ小屋の掃除 毎日やるからさ
Come on, please?!
ねえ いいでしょ？
ねえったら ねえねえねえ…
Please, please, please?!
（発砲音）
（男たちの笑い声）
（トニスの泣き声）
（男Ａ）フンッ
"Vash the Stampede,
The Humanoid Typhoon...
ヒューマノイド･タイフーン
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
...Taken Down In Inepril City."
Nice headline!
アイプリルシティの片田舎に落つ
ってか
（男たちの笑い声）
（男Ｄ）やったぜ
600億ダブドルだ！ ハハッ
We did it!
$ $60,000,000,000!
（男Ｂ）カーッ たまんねえぜ
This is great!
Now we'll be famous
across the entire galaxy!
（男Ａ）これで俺たちの名前も
星中にとどろくってもんだ
ハハハ… ああ？
You're acting awful cautious.
It's okay, he's dead!
なんでえ
えらく慎重じゃねえかよ
大丈夫 しとめたって
（男Ｃ）ヘヘッ
相手が相手だからねえ
Yeah, but it's him lying there...
（男Ｃ）えっ！
Hey, girls! Don't look so glum!
（男Ａ）よう ねえちゃんたちよ
しけた面すんなって
こんな店 建て替えてやっても
いいんだぜ えっ
We can have this restaurant
rebuilt if you want!
Do you mean it?!
（ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード）
ホント？
（男Ａ）ヘヘヘヘ… あたぼうよ
Damn straight! Each one of us
is a multi-billionaire now.
こちとら
600億ダブドルの億万長者…
What a relief!
I was so worried about that.
（ヴァッシュ）そいつはよかった
気になってたんだわ
（においを嗅ぐ音）
You smell like a tomato!
トマト臭(くせ)え
It got dumped on me
when I tried to scramble.
逃げようとした拍子に
頭からかぶったんだ
Can I bill you for dry cleaning?
クリーニング代 請求しても
いいかな？
No, but I'll give you
something better.
（男Ａ）
いいや 別のもんくれてやる
A one-way ticket to Heaven!!
天国までの片道切符だ！
（パンッという音）
（２人）ううっ
（４人）うわあ…
ハア… せっかちすぎる
Such impatience...
Come on, let's not be so hasty!
Let's talk it over!
まあ そう結論を急がずに
話し合いましょう
Who the heck are you?!
何者(なにもん)だよ あんた
Oh, self-introductions
are so embarrassing...
いやー 自己紹介なんて
テレますけど—
あえて言うとするなら—
But if I must, I am a hunter of peace
who chases the mayfly known as love...
愛というカゲロウを追い続ける
平和の狩人
...or something like that.
…みたいな感じ
（４人）ああ…
I'll kill the bugger now!!
（男Ａ）てめえ ぶち殺す！
Don't do it, stupid!
Do you wanna die?!
（男Ｃ）よせバカ
命がいらねえのかよ
さっきので俺たちは死んでんだ
He just killed us all!
The next time, he'll use real bullets!!
今度はモノホンが来るぞ
Shoot me if you want!
Go nuts.
撃つなら撃ちなさい
ドーンとね
（男Ｃ）うわあー！
挑発すんなよ 狩人さんよ
- What did you say?!
- Don't provoke him, hunter!
（空撃ちする音）
（男Ａ）ああ…
Give it up! Except for this guy,
you all used up your bullets already.
無理無理
だって この人以外
さっき全弾 撃っちゃってんだもん
ええっ？
How can you tell?
なんで分かんのよ？
（ヴァッシュ）数えてた
I counted.
Geez, it's not like
I'm a highway robber...
なにも身ぐるみ置いていかなくても
いいのにな
（トニス）エヘッ
Here. It really helped!
はい 助かったよ
ありがとう
Thanks.
うわあっ
Wow!
That was very impressive!
（店主）大した腕じゃのう
Have you always survived
without shooting like that?
あんた ああやって
撃たずに生きてきたのかね？
Mm-hmm!
'Cause it's too wasteful!
（ヴァッシュ）
モグモグ モグモグ…
だって
もったいないじゃないですか
For the price of one bullet,
I can eat four hotcakes!
弾丸１発のお値段で—
ホットケーキ ４枚
食べられるんですよ
You're a strange one.
変わったやつじゃ
And you call yourself a gunman?
それでガンマンが務まるのかい？
I really should change my ways!
ダメですよねえ アハハハ…
ハハハハ…
アハハハ…
I'm sorry.
（モニカ）ごめんなさい
Huh?
えっ？
You are Mr. Vash the Stampede,
aren't you?
あんた—
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードさん
なんじゃろ？
えっ？
I'm sorry.
Please die without a fuss.
（店主）すまんが
何も言わずに死んでくれ
I'm sorry, Mr. Vash!
ごめんなさい ヴァッシュさん
Uh? Oh...
えっ あのう…
（風の音）
Ma'am, half of the city
is buried in sand!
（ミリィ･トンプソン）
先輩 町の半分が砂に飲まれてます
（メリル･ストライフ）
きっと壊れて停止した
プラントがあるんですわ
Their plant probably
broke down and stopped working.
Then they should fix it.
（ミリィ）直せばいいのに
（メリル）
プラントのメンテナンスに
いくらかかると思ってるの？
Do you know how much
plant maintenance costs?
What?! Is it expensive?
えっ 高いんですか？
ハア…
（衝撃音）
（メリル）あっ
（サイレン）
This time, it's just
like we were informed!
（ミリィ）
今回は情報どおりみたいですね
（メリル）フフッ
（ミリィ）先輩 笑ってる
You're smiling, ma'am.
えっ？ そ… そんなこと
ないですわよ
Huh?
N-No, I'm not!
Now, quickly! We have to
confirm and prevent risks!
早速 情報確認とリスク回避ですわ
This time, we will find
the real Vash the Stampede!
今度こそ 本物の—
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードを
見つけますわよ
のお〜
うぎゃあー ダメかね
Is there no end?!
（骨が折れる音）
（ヴァッシュ）うう…
There he is!! In here!
（市民Ａ）いたぞ！ ここだ
（ヴァッシュ）マズ
Oh, crap!
（発砲音）
（ヴァッシュ）うわあー
Shoot him!
（市民Ａ）当たれ！
- There he is!
- We found you!
（女性Ａ）いたわ
（女性Ｂ）みーつけた
Do you mean me?
フッ 僕のことかい？
（発砲音）
（ヴァッシュ）またかー
Get him!
Not again!!!
- That bastard! Kill him!
- Where did he go?!
（市民たち）
こっちだ！ こっちにいたぞ
Everyone is so animated today.
にぎやかな日だねえ
（黒猫の鳴き声）
なぜ僕がこんな目に遭うの？ ママ
Why does this happen to me, Maman?
I haven't done anything wrong, but
everybody always picks on me, Maman!
何も悪いことしてないのに
みんなが僕をいじめるよ ママ
But now isn't the time
to be bawling in French.
…なーんて フランス語で
泣き入れてる場合じゃ
うひゃー！
（鐘にぶつかる音）
（ヴァッシュ）ああ…
There he is!
He's up there!!
（市民Ｂ）
あそこだ！ あそこにいるぞ
He's mine!
（市民Ｃ）いったれー
（発砲音）
I can't take it anymore!!
（ヴァッシュ）もうイヤー
（発砲音）
They're getting
really heated up, ma'am!
（ミリィ）ずいぶんヒートアップ
してるみたいですね 先輩
We have to do something
before the whole city is blown away.
（メリル）急がなきゃ
このままほっとくと
町ごと消し飛びますわ
But if they're this excited...
（メリル）
しかし これだけの騒ぎ…
本物かもしれない
... it might really be him.
We're going to stop the riot!
Come on, Milly!
騒ぎを止めます
行くわよ ミリィ
あっ 待ってください 先輩
Wait, ma'am!
Ma'am!!
先輩！
（爆発音）
（市民Ｄ）うわー 痛(いて)えー
OW!
It hurts like crazy all over!!
体じゅう むちゃくちゃ痛え
（市民Ｅ）誰だ？
グレネードなんか使いやがったのは
Who the hell used a grenade?!
They can't identify him from
a pile of pulp, you dumb ass!
（市民Ｆ）しとめても
見分けがつかなきゃ—
意味ねえんだぜ おい
This is bad! These people
are out of control!
（ミリィ）ヤバいですよ
ここの人たち理性失ってます
うん…
Your attention, please!
ご町内の皆様 お取り込み中
大変申し訳ございません
I am extremely sorry to disturb you!
I am Meryl Stryfe from
the Bernardelli Insurance Society!
私(わたくし) ベルナルデリ保険協会の
メリル･ストライフと…
（爆発音）
（２人）うわっ
（発砲音）
（ミリィ）ひいっ
The man you are after,
Vash the Stampede...
皆様が追っている—
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードは
危険な男です
...is a dangerous man!
In order to protect your
precious lives and possessions...
皆様の大切な命や財産を
守るためにも…
（放送案内のチャイム）
Message from Mission Control!
（ヘンリー）
対策本部より連絡します
Temporarily suspend
all pursuit of Vash!
ヴァッシュ捕獲作戦は
一時中断します
Everybody proceed to base!
皆さん 本部に集合してください
Suspend temporarily?!
That's not funny!
一時中断？
冗談じゃない
即刻中止よ！
Cease this permanently!!
（市民たちのざわめき）
What do we do now, Chairman?
（ヘンリー）
どうするんですか？ 会長
The damage and casualties
are just getting worse!
このままではケガ人や被害が
増える一方です
（会長）ああ ４時間以上戦っても
まだ しとめられんとは…
I can't believe we still
haven't got him after four hours...
Got him, nothing!
He's managing to run away...
（ヘンリー）それどころか—
あの男は我々に対して
１発も撃ち返さず逃げ延びてます
...without returning
a single bullet!
He's too strong.
If we make him mad, we're dead.
格が違いすぎたか
もし あいつが本気になったら…
Chairman, perhaps we should stop this
while the city is still standing!
（ヘンリー）
会長 町が形のあるうちに
やめるべきでは？
That goes without saying!
（メリル）当然ですわ
Where is the man in charge?
責任者の方は
いらっしゃいまして？
Who are you people?!
誰だ？ 君たちは
Let me see the man in charge!
責任者を出してください！
（大きな足音）
（メリル）なんて大それたことを
するんですの！
How could you commit
such an outrage?!
You couldn't take down
The Humanoid Typhoon...
ヒューマノイド･タイフーン
相手に—
...no matter how many thousands
of people you set on him!
あなたたちが何千人集まっても
かなうわけありませんわ！
いや 確かに
リスクの高い賭けかもしれん
Yes, the risk is very high...
...but we really need
that $ $60,000,000,000!
だが わしらはどうしても
600億ダブドルが必要なんじゃ
あっ プラントのため… ですのね？
It's for the plant, isn't it?
That's right. Over half
of the plant is unusable...
（ヘンリー）そうだ
維持システムのバグで—
...due to a support system bug.
半分以上のプラントが
使いものにならなくなった
But if you mess with Mr. Vash
and the city gets wrecked...
でも ヴァッシュさんに手を出して
町がめちゃくちゃになったら—
...you'll have more than
the plant to worry about.
プラントどころの話じゃ
ないですよね
Oh, no...
（会長）ヤバい
（一同）えっ？
It may already be too late.
（会長）もう手遅れかも…
I thought we should fight fire
with fire, so I used our last resort.
わし
毒には毒と思って—
最後の手段
使っちゃったよ
What is our last resort?
最後の手段て何なんですか？
That.
（会長）あれ
（一同）あれ？
（近づく大きな足音）
（ゴフセフ）ゴアアーッ
（蒸気が噴き出す音）
終わりだ… 終わった
It's over.
It's all over.
ゴアアーッ！
W-W-Who, what is that?!
なな… 何者ですの？
あいつ
ネブラスカ親子
The Nebraska Family!
（ネブラスカ）だだ… 誰だ！
こんな所に車止めたのは
Who parked this car here?!
息子が蹴つまずくだろうが
のけ のけ！
You wanna trip my son or what?!
Move it, now!!
Damned ignorant drivers!
愚民＆愚車両
Let me borrow that!
（ヘンリー）
ちょっとお貸しください
What are you doing here?!
お前たち
なんで こんな所にいるんだ！
Both of you are supposed to
be locked away for 700 years!!
700年の懲役で
２人とも塀の中だろう
じゃかあしいわ
Shut yer trap!!
昨日 自主的に切り上げてきたのよ
We released ourselves
for good behavior yesterday!
だ… 脱獄だろう それは
Th-That's called a jailbreak!
ヒヒヒヒッ せっかく静かな所で
のんびりしてたのになあ
Too bad, I was getting quite
fond of the quiet life, too!
600億ダブドルが
転がってくるとなりゃ—
But who can lie idle knowing that
$ $60 billion is there for the taking?
のんきに寝ている場合じゃねえよな
Right, Gofsef?
そうだろ？ ゴフセフ
（ゴフセフ）ブオーッ
The Nebraska Family...
ネブラスカファミリー
...felons of over 150
Class A offenses...
Ａ級犯罪件数150を超える
重犯罪人… って
Hey!
Don't tell me you plan to
sic that big man on him.
まさか あのビッグマンを
ぶつけようってんじゃ…
いいアイデアだと
思ったんだよねえ
It seemed like a
good idea at the time.
（メリル）ううっ
It's unforgivable!
許せなーい！
Why does every situation we run into
always take the worst possible turn?!
なんで こう状況が
悪い方向ばっかり行くんですの？
We caught Vash the Stampede!
（サンディ）
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードを
捕まえました
（メリル）えっ
Huh?
We caught Vash the Stampede!
（サンディ）
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードを
捕まえました
えっ？
Eh?
We caught Vash the Stampede!!
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードを
捕まえました
You caught him?!
“捕まえました”って…
ハア ハア ハア…
ハア ハア…
みんな あきらめてくれたのかな？
Maybe they've all given up.
ああ？
プハーッ 生き返った
I'm alive again!
えっ？
Don't move!
動かないで！
Oh?
（ヴァッシュ）あらら… あらら
Oh.
Sandy, go and tell Control
we've caught Vash the Stampede!
（モニカ）サンディ
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードを
捕まえたって—
本部に伝えてちょうだい
（サンディ）はーい！
Right!
Be quick!
急いでね
（ヴァッシュ）
エプロン姿の賞金稼ぎか
Bounty hunters in aprons?
Wouldn't want children to see this.
子どもには見せられない
That's right, we don't
want them to see this!
（主婦Ａ）
そうさ 見せたくなんかない
But we desperately need money!
でもね 私たちには
お金が必要なんだ
I have a son lying sick at home.
家には 病気の息子が寝てるんだよ
But the doctor took off
and abandoned this dying city!
でも 死んでいくこの町を捨てて
医者はどこかに行っちまったんだ
There's no one left in this
city I can take him to!
あの子を見る人間が
この町にはいないんだよ
That's why, I... I...
だから だから…
Everyone and everything went wrong
after the plant malfunctioned!
（主婦Ｂ）プラントの異常で—
人も土地も何もかも
ダメになったの
But not everyone is rich
enough to leave the city!
（主婦Ｃ）だからといって
町を出られる人間はそういやしない
We need money to call the
engineers to fix the plant!
（主婦Ｂ）
プラントを直す技師を呼ぶために
お金がいるのよ
If we don't fix it,
this city is through!
直せなければ この町は終わりよ
Along with everyone in it.
町のみんなもね
Your sacrifice
can save this city.
（モニカ）あなた一人で
この町を救えるの
So please let us take you in!
だから お願い 捕まって
Don't move!
動かないで！
I understand your situation well...
事情は とてもよく分かるよ
でも…
...but...
Please, don't move!!
お願い 動かないで！
Until I see him...
（ヴァッシュ）
やつに会うまで 俺は—
...I...
立ち止まるわけにはいかないんだ
...have to keep moving!
ハア ハア ハア…
Please...
（ヴァッシュ）
頼む 撃たせないでくれ
...don't make me shoot you.
頼む
Please.
（衝撃音）
みんな 伏せろ！
Everybody, down!!
（衝撃音）
（メリル）あっ
Over there...
（メリル）あそこに…
（ミリィ）先輩
Ma'am!
Vash the Stampede is over there!
（メリル）あそこに
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードが…
Bingo!
ビンゴ！
It was so easy! Too easy!
ちょろい ちょろすぎるわ
Are you sunk
after only one shot?
この１発でおだぶつか？
That's funny! That's so funny!
笑う 笑うよなあ
（ネブラスカ）イヤッハハハ…
（ゴフセフ）うわああっ
（機械のモーター音）
（ゴフセフ）うおおーっ
Where is Vash the Stampede?
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードは…
（ゴフセフ）うああっ
えっ？
What the?
なんじゃ？
おおっ！
あっ
That's him.
The Devil's helper...
（メリル）いるのね
100万人都市の１つを灰に変えた—
... who reduced one of
the great cities to ashes!
悪魔の使い
The legendary outlaw,
Vash the Stampede...
伝説の賞金首—
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードが
あの向こうに
... is just over there.
あっ
ああ…
Th...
（メリル）そっ そんな…
That...
That can't be!
ウソよー
ヘヘヘッ そう来なくちゃ
Now that's more like it!
Hey... Why is everybody
getting the wrong idea?
（メリル）ちょっと
みんな 何 勘違いしてるんですのよ
That can't be him!
あの人が本物なわけないじゃない
Vash the Stampede
is a horrible fiend.
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードは
恐ろしい悪魔ですのよ
関われば町が破壊され—
If you get in his way,
he can destroy cities...
... and get out of the worst
situations imaginable!
どんな状況からも切り抜ける
Even if it hails bullets on him...
Even if he is against 1,000 men...
銃弾の雨にさらされても
たとえ千人を相手にしても
... he will emerge
without a scratch.
ケガひとつしない男
それが それが…
That's... That's who...
What now,
Vash the Stampede?
（ネブラスカ）どうする！
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
あっ
That's...
それが…
...Vash the Stampede!
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
What's the matter, buddy boy?
You chickening out?
どうした おら！
逃げるのか？ えっ？
えっ？
おうおう… 優しいんだねえ
You're a real nice guy.
Time's up!
タイムリミット
Throw the fear of
death into him, Gofsef!
いっちょ脅したれ ゴフセフ
（ゴフセフ）だーっ
（発砲音）
（メリル）あっ
（ゴフセフ）ブンッ
Mommy!!
（サンディ）お母ちゃん！
That damned Nebraska
is a loose cannon!
ネブラスカのやつ
無茶がすぎるぞ
I don't want any fatalities...
死人だけは勘弁してくれ
なんてことを！
How could you?!
アハハハハ…
えっ？
（どよめき）
アハッ
なんだ ピンピンしとるじゃないか
Aw, you're doing just fine!
I was hoping you'd ditch the woman
and save your own skin!
いいとこ女をほっぽって
トンズラ決めると思ったがな
ヴァッシュさんは
そんな人じゃないです
Mr. Vash isn't that
sort of a person!
Come to think of it...
（メリル）そういえば あの人…
（ネブラスカ）ヘンッ
あくまでも殺さずってわけかよ
So you won't kill,
no matter what?
You're disgusting!
気持ち悪いやつ
However, that makes
you a hypocrite!
だがな おめえのそれは偽善だ
えっ？
I know at some point you've killed
those who gave you a hard time.
（ネブラスカ）絶対どこかで—
不都合を並べたやつを
消してきてんのさ
How do I know?
なぜなら 現におめえは
消される側に回ってねえ
Because you haven't yet
had your turn to be killed!
The $ $60,000,000,000 reward
on your head is proof!
おめえに懸かってる
600億ダブドルの賞金が—
なによりの証拠だ
What do you
say to that?!
ええ どうなんだよ！
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
Vash the Stampede!
Why won't he say anything?
なんでやつは黙ってる？
Why is he taking
that kind of abuse?!
あそこまで言われて
なぜ言い返さねえ
ヘッ
えっ？
So you're finally ready to fight!
（ネブラスカ）
やっと その気になったようだな
Oh, you wanna draw?
おっ 抜くか？
It's pointless, no matter
what calibre pistol you use!
意味ねえぞ
どんな大口径の銃でも—
You can't stop a car
ramming at 120 iles an hour!
200アイルで突っ込んでくる車は
止められねえ
You've felt it twice already!
Even your measly brain can realize...
２度も食らってんだ
息子のげんこつが
そんなもんじゃねえことぐらい—
...that my son's fist is
a force to be reckoned with!
てめえのウスラ頭でも分かるよな
This is your last chance to run!
Although, no matter how fast you run...
逃げるなら今のうちだぞ
もっとも
どんなに速く走ったところで—
...the next thing you know,
you'll be in tiny pieces!
気がついた次の瞬間
バラバラだがな
Now pay attention,
for I am about to lecture you...
いいか これから俺様が—
...on just how much of
a fool you really are!
お前がどれだけ愚かか
レクチャーしてやる
こいつでな
Using this!
My Human Mincemeat
Special Course!
人間ミンチのスペシャルコースだ
（ヴァッシュ）うわっ
（ネブラスカ）早く助けに行け
Go help them, quick!
And then die in the
most humiliating way!
そして一番みっともない死にざまを
さらせや
（ゴフセフ）ドオン
（ゴフセフ）ブオオーン！
うあああーっ
No way!
えっ？ ウソ
He changed its course!
そ… そらせた
That was great!
すごーい
ガーッ
て… 鉄砲玉６発で
息子のげんこつ そらしやがった
He veered off my son's fist
with six bullets!
Not quite.
違うな
I have one left.
It's a special one.
まだ１発残ってる
スペシャルなのがな
なあ…
（銃声）
（ゴフセフ）うおっ
うっ うう… ああーっ
What?!
（市民たちの悲鳴）
（どよめき）
アハハ…
Ma'am, ma'am! He really beat him!!
I don't believe it!!
せ… 先輩 ホントに
やっちゃいましたよ あの人
しかも たった６発の鉄砲玉だけで
And he did it with
only six bullets!
Suddenly it's very clear to me...
（メリル）
今 はっきり分かったわ
あの人が—
...why he's called
The Humanoid Typhoon.
ヒューマノイド･タイフーンと
呼ばれるわけが
It's him...
あの人が… あの人が
本物のヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
He's the real...
...Vash the Stampede!
You're amazing!
（トニス）すごいや
（２人）アハハハ…
I'm not amazing.
すごくなんかないよ
全然すごくなんかないさ
I'm not amazing at all.
It ain't over yet!
（ネブラスカ）まだ終わってねえ
（おもちゃの銃の音）
えっ？ あれ？
Wha?
That's twice you've
saved me today!
今日 ２度目だね
（トニス）エヘヘ…
Don't ignore me, you!
（ネブラスカ）無視するな おら！
D-Don't think you've w-won,
e-even for a s-s...
て… てめえ
これで勝ったと… 勝ったと
Let's call it quits already!
（ヴァッシュ）もうやめましょうよ
（ネブラスカ）えっ？
After all,
this land is made of...
だって この世は
ラブ＆ピースだ！
...love & peace!
へえ？
はあ？
ラブ＆ピース！
Love & peace! Love & peace!
（３人）ラブ＆ピース！
Love & peace!
アハハ…
Again!
W-What is he d...
なっ 何 言って…
Ma'am! Our report, our report!
先輩 報告書 報告書！
えっ？
Uh?
（３人）ラブ＆ピース！
Report.
“報告書”
4 months and 12 days
after receiving our orders...
“辞令が下りてから
４か月と12日目に—”
...we achieved contact
with our target, Vash...
“ターゲットであるヴァッシュ…”
...contact with our target,
Vash the...
“ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードとの
接触に… 接触に…”
...the...
ラブ＆ピース！
No! This can't be real!!!
イヤー こんな現実はイヤー！
Now, everybody join along!
（ヴァッシュ）
さあ皆さん ご一緒に
Love & Peace!!!
ラブ＆ピース！
♪〜
〜♪
（ヴァッシュ）
思いを抱き続けた年月が
長ければ長いほど—
The longer one
holds onto a memory...
...the longer one
lives in the past.
人は過去を生きる糧とする
The deeper the memory
they hold onto is...
抱き続けた思いが深ければ深いほど
人は過去を美しく磨きあげる
...the more beautiful
the past will become.
美化された思いは
やがて憎しみへとその姿を変える
The beautified memories will
eventually turn into hate...
Even if they look ahead,
they lose the ability to walk.
前を向いても
歩くことができなくなる
As long as the heavy chain called
Revenge continues to fetter the heart.
復讐(ふくしゅう)という名の重い鎖が
心を縛り続けるかぎり
悲しみの涙が流れ続けるかぎり
As long as the tears of sadness
continue to flow.